Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2019 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013; 172383
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence, 190087
    - Ward, Undated; 208440 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Wark, Jane, 2005-2006; 208441 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Warren, Bryan / Speed Art Museum, 2001; 208442 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Watanabe, Micki, 2000-2007; 208443 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Waters, Jack, 1992; 208444 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Watson, Jane D., 1991-1992; 208445 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Watson, Steven, 1995-1997; Undated; 208446 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Watson, Steven and Robert Atkins, 1997-2001; 208447 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Watt, Ken, 2005; 208448 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Waving, Hannah, 2001; 208449 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Weaver, Lois, 2004; 208450 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - The Webster Apartments, 1968; 208451 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Weems, Marianne / The Builders Association, 1997-2004; 208452 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Wehiver, Elisabeth, 1988; 208453 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Weiner, Lawrence, 1977-1992; Undated; 208454 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Weis, Adrienne, 1981; 208455 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Weisberg, Arnold, Undated; 208456 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Weiss, Ted, 1992; 208457 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Weissberg, Jed, 1993; 208458 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Welch, Roger, 1987; 208459 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Weller, Marjorie More, Undated; 208460 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Wendy, 1984; 208461 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Wesman, Jane, 1995; 208462 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Wessel, John, 1985; 208463 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - West, Rosie, 2001; 208464 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - West, Troy, 1984; 208465 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Westcoast, Wanda, 1983; 208466 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Westreich, Thea, 1984; 208467 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Weymouth, Sheilagh and Kathy Kelly Christos, 1997-2005; Undated; 208468 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Wheeler, Britta, 1998-2007; 208469 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Wheeler and Powell, [Britta and H.], 1997-2005; 208470 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Wheeler, Susan, 1986; 208471 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - White, David, 1992; 208472 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - White, Gina, 1965-2002; 208473 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - White, Maria / Tate Gallery Library, 1995; 208474 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - White, Robin / Printed Matter, 1991; 208475 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - White, Stephen B., 1995; Undated; 208476 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Whitman, Deborah, 1981-1991; 208477 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Whitney Museum, 2001; 208485 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Whyte, Ryan, 1998; 208486 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Wickson, Kathy, 1977; 208487 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Wiebke, Gary, 1990; 208488 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Wilkins, Will, 2002; 208489 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Williams, Pat, undated; 208490 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Williams, Reese, 1988; 208491 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Williams, Tom, 1985-1988; 208492 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Williamson/Scarbrough (Amanda), 1998, illegible; 208493 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Willis, Mike, undated; 208495 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Wilmington College, 1965-1968; 208497 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1964-1965; 208498 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1965; 208499 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1966; 208500 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1966; 208501 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1967; 208502 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1967; 208503 (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1968; 208504 (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1968; 208505 (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1968; 208506 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1969; 208507 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1969; 208508 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, [undated 60's], 70's; 208509 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1970; 208510 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1971; 208511 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1972; 208765 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1973; 208766 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW, 1974; 208767 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1975; 208768 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1976; 208769 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur (also contains material from MSW), 1977; 208770 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1978; 208771 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1979; 208772 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, Alice and Arthur, 1980; 208773 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - to M.R.S.Wilson, Barbara, 1985; 208775 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, Betty and Paul, 1981-1985, undated; 208776 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Wilson, Bob and Doris, 1972; 208777 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Wilson, Bob and Doris (also contains materials from MSW), 1965-1967; 208778 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Wilson, Bob and Doris, 1975-1988, undated; 208779 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Callie Wilson, 1964-1965; 208780 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Callie Wilson, 1965-1966; 208781 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1964; 208782 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1965; 208783 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1965-1966; 208784 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Wilson, Callie, ca. 1966; 208785 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Wilson, Callie, Jan - July 1966; 208786 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Wilson, Callie, Aug - Dec 1966; 208787 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1966-1967; 208788 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1967; 208789 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1967-1968; 208790 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Wilson, Callie, Undated (circa 1966-1968); 208791 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Wilson, Callie (also contains materials from MSW), 1965- 1968, Undated; 208792 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Wilson, Callie (also contains materials from Alice Wilson to Callie), 1968-1969; 208512 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1970, undated; 208793 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Callie, letters to Alice and Arthur, 1970-1971; 208794 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1971; 208834 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1972, undated; 208837 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Callie, ca. 1973 -; 208838 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Callie (letters to Alice and Arthur Wilson), 1973-1979; 208866 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Callie (letter with enclosures), 1975; 208867 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Callie, Undated, (ca. 1973-1975); 208868 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Callie (also contains material from Martha), 1975-1977; 208869 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1977; 208870 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1978-1982, undated; 208871 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Enclosure- letter from Callie Wilson, 9/27/1986; 208872 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Callie (also contains materials from MSW), 1983-1986; 208873 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, Callie, (1986-1994) undated; 208874 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1987-1988; 208875 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, Callie (re. Comly's birth/adoption also contains materials from Wilson), 1988, undated; 208876 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Letter from Callie Wilson, August 13, 1988; 208880 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1989-1990; 208881 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1991; 208882 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1992-1993; 208883 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1993-1994; 208884 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1995; 208885 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1987-1996, undated; 208886 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1997, undated; 208887 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Wilson, Callie, 1997-1998; 208888 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Wilson, Callie, postmark illegible; 208889 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Wilson, Callie, 2000-2001; 208890 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Wilson, Callie, 2002-2003; 208892 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Wilson, Callie, 2004; 208893 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Wilson, Callie, 2007-2008; 208896 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Wilson, Callie, Undated; 208906 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Wilson, Callie and Alice, 1980; 208907 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Wilson, Charis, 1994; Undated; 208908 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Wilson, Doris, 1985-2008; Undated; 208909 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Wilson, Nancie and Paul, 1966-1972; 208910 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Wilson, Paul (also contains material from Martha Wilson), 1980-1995; 208911 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Wilkins, Will K., Undated; 208912 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Wineman, John, 1984; 208913 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Wingard, Sheila / Penn State, 1996; 208914 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Winters, Lynne / NSSR / Seeing American, 1997; 208915 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - [Winthier], Jim, 1992; 208916 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - The Wise Family, 1989; 208917 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Withers. Josephine, 1993; 208918 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Wittels, Lauren / Regency Arts Press, 2006; 208919 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Who's Who in American Art, Undated; 208920 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Wolcott, Mart, 1989-1998; 208921 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Wolff-Stanton, Gerri and Heidi, Undated; 208922 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Wong, Maureen, 1994-1995; 208923 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Wood, Reid (with enclosure), 2003; 208924 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Woodman, Elizabeth (Aunt Elizabeth), 1965-1980; 208925 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Woodman, JoAnn and Lew, 1990-2002; Undated; 208926 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Woodward, Judy, 2007; 208927 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Working Families Party, 2002; 208928 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Wortzel, Adrianne, 1998; 208929 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Woznuah, Deborah, Undated; 208930 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Wright, Charles, 1993; 208931 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Wright, Fred and Sam, 1977; 208932 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Wright, Haviland, 1998; Undated; 208933 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Wright, Rae, 1997; 208934 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Wu, Alice, 1998-2009; Undated; 208935 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Wunch, Oliver, 2007; 208936 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Wyatt, Susan / Artists Space, 1979-1995; 208937 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Yale - New Haven Occupational Medicine Program / Dr. Mark Cullen, 1989; 208938 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Yankowitz, Holden, 1990; 208939 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Yassky, Brahna and Bruce Javasky, 1985-2005; 209007 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Yassky, James, 1990, undated; 209008 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Yassky, James and George Piette, 1983-1991; 209009 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Yeh, Tzu-Chi (Effi and Chi), 1989; 209010 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Yoshimoto, Midori, 2005; 209011 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Young, Frank, 1987; 209012 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Yvonne, undated; 209013 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Zabielskis, Peter, 1976; 209014 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Zaloom, Paul, 1999; 209015 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Zamudio, Raul and Nathan Blake, 1994-2005; 209016 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Zamudia-Taylor, Victor, 1995; 209017 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Zareleski, Krysztof, undated; 209018 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Zaret, Michael, undated; 209019 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Zaret, Michael (packet from), 1968; 209020 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Zaza, David, 2000; 209021 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - The Zelevanskys, undated; 209022 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Zeller, Donna, 1994; 209023 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Zempel, Jerilea, undated; 209024 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Ziff, Janet, 1983-1998; 209025 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Ziff, Janet and Leonard Berman, 1987-1993; 209026 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Zigun, Dick, 2005; 209027 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Zippi, Daniel/Creative Time, 1993; 209028 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Zirin, Nola, undated; 209029 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Zorreguieta, Dolores, 1997-2006; 209030 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Zucker, Barbara, undated; 209031 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Zwicker, Tony, 1999; 209032 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Zwicker, Tony, 1999; 209033 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Un-alphabetized correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 83, Folder 1-26)
    - Un-alphabetized correspondence, 1971-1975; 2006-2013 (Box 84, Folder 1-30)
    - Un-alphabetized correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 85, Folder 1-6)
    - Un-alphabetized correspondence, 2007-2013 (Box 86, Folder 20-25)
  - Subseries B: Comly Correspondence, 190089
    Subseries B contains correspondence to Wilson's son Comly as a child, dating from 1989 to 2007.
    The letters in this sub-series are arranged alphabetically.
    - About Comley, various; 209036 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence to and from Comley, Various; 209087 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence to and from Comley, Various; 209088 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence to Comley, Various; 209089 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence to Comley, Various; 209090 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Comly School, 1992-2001; 209091 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Comly, Undated; 209092 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Comly - from Mr. and Mrs. Richard S. Cook (granddad and grammie), 1989-1995; 209093 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Comly - from Cook, Scott, 1990-2000; Undated; 209094 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Comly - from Wilson, Callie, 1990-2007; 209095 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Comly - from Wilson, Martha, 2000; Undated; 209096 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - P.S. 234 and Downtown Day Camp correspondence, 1994-2000; 209097 (Box 23, Folder 58)
- Series III: Subject Files, 1960-2011; 181023; 3 videodiscs (dvd); 700 Megabytes in one computer disc.
  The material in this series maintains the original order in which it was received. The series is divided topically into eight subseries, and then alphabetically within each subseries.
  - Subseries A: Art and Personal Files, 181032
    - 1987 House in Poconos, 1987; undated; 267647 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 1988 Stuff I Used to Carry Around With Me, 1988; undated; 267648 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - 1989 Research Notes (1/2), 1989-1990; 209099 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - 1989 Research Note[s] (2/2), 1989-1990; 209100 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 1996 Reno and correspondence with old (1997) partnership, 1996-1997; 209101 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 1999 Paradise, 209102 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - 2007 1998-9, 1998-2007; 209103 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Abbeville Press Envelope, 1987; 209104 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Angelika Fester - Cambridge Guide to American Theater, 1992; 209105 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Annie Doran, 1984; 209106 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Appearance as Value in Video Primer, 2001; 209107 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Art Business Correspondence, 1976-1982; 209108 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Art Business Correspondence, 1972-summer, 1975 (1/2), 1972-1975; 209109 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Art Business Correspondence, 1972-summer, 1975 (2/2), 1972-1975; 209110 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Art Equipment Correspondence, 1974-1977, undated; 209111 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Art Journal correspondence (1/4), 1991-1993; 209112 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Art Journal correspondence (2/4), 1992-1993; 209113 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Art Journal correspondence (3/4), 1991-1993; 209114 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Art Journal correspondence (4/4), 1993-1995; 209115 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Art Magazine correspondence, 1977, 1979, 1980; 209116 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Art and Philosophy of Language, undated; 209117 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Art and Politics course, 2008-2009 (Box 88, Folder 22-23)
      - Cave Excerpts - video recording, undated; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box Shared Fales 007)
    - Art and Psychology, 1971, 1976; 209118 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Art-Rite, 1976; 209119 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Artists' books, 2008-2010 (Box 86, Folder 12-14)
    - Artwork by J. McClurg, 1977, 1985; 267649 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Artworks Rec'd NSCAD, 1971; 209120 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Astrolo (1/2), ca. 1989-1994; 209121 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Astrolo (2/2), ca. 1987-1994; 209122 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Astrology, 1995-1996 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
    - Astrology, 1996-1998; 209123 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Backflip by Katy Kennedy: A Draft, 2001; 209124 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Backflip proposal, 2000; 209125 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Barbara Bush and Carnegie Mellon University separated at Birth, 2006; 209151 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - "Barbara Bush on Abuse" text CAA mtg 2/21/91, 1991; 216817 (Box 25, Folder 1A)
    - Barbara Bush photo & neg from Cooper Union Jan. 92 Paula Court, 1992; 209152 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Barbara Bush in Style section of TNYT, 1992., 209153 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - B. Bush at NYU 12/7/99 announcement: Inverted Odysseys, 1999; 209204 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Baruch/Johanna Reusch, student records [RESTRICTED], 1999; 209205 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Material pertaining to individual student records may be restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with specific questions regarding access to such records.
    - Belgium and Italy 4/20-27/2008, 209250 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Biz 2001-2002, 2004 (1/2), 2001-2004; 209251 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Biz 2001-2002, 2004 (2/2), 2001-2004; 209252 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Boca Museum Text, 1991; 209253 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Book Reviews, 1980; 209254 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn College Essays by Students [RESTRICTED], 209279 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Coll. (1/4), 1975; 209286 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Coll. (2/4), 1974-1975; 209287 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn Coll (3/4), 1975; 209290 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Brooklyn Coll. (4/4), 1975; 209291 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn 20th Cent., 1975; 209294 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Building Histories Show, Apex, Oct. 99, 1999; 209296 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Bulletin Board 1984-1986, 209292 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - From Bulletin Board, 1981; 209293 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Business, Gigs (1/2), 1977-1980; 209297 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Business, Gigs (2/2), 1975; 209298 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - CAA [biz], 1990-1993; 209378 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - CAA w/ B. Bush, July - Aug. 1992, 209379 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - CAA Art Journal issue on performance art, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - CAA Intro 12/7/96, 1996; 209380 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Calendar stuff, 1960-1990; 209381 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Catalog of Exchance Resource, Belfast 1995, 1997; 209388 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Cats, 1981-1985; 209389 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Cat Lover's Photograph Album, Undated; 267650 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Censorship [Comm.] (1/2), 1989-1996; 209390 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Censorship [Comm.] (2/2), 1989-1996; 209391 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Chelsea Deal 97, 1997; 209392 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - College of Fine Arts, Arizona State University, 1995; 209393 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Consulting and Perf research 2002., 209513 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Contemporarea Nancy Reagan Oct. 1990, 209514 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cooper Union brochure, 1994 w/ Tipper Gore, 209515 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Copyright, undated; 209516 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Corcoran, 1989-1990; 209517 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Courts, 1981; 209518 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1974-75; 267651 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Creative Artist Public Services Programs (CAPS) and Grants, 1975-1976; 267652 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1975-1980; 267653 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1976-1977; 267654 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1977-1978; 267655 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1978-1982; 267656 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, Undated; 267657 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Current Biz 6/97-, 1997-1999; 209519 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - DCA Artist Certification, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Develop Don't Destroy Brooklyn, 2005-2008 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Diary Stuff from Houseboat, Undated; 267658 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Dick Higgins, 1998; 209522 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Disband Songs, 1978-1982, undated; 209523 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Documenta Archiv, undated; 209524 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Dr. Rafael Montanez Ortiz, undated; 209525 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Encyclopedia Americana (contains disc), 1998; 209526 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - English, General, Mar. 22, 1976; 209527 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - envelope labeled Barbara Kirschenblatt-Gimblett articles and papers, undated; 209528 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Exalicers, 1977; 209529 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Exercise, undated; 209530 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Fales Library Dinner April 12, 2000, 209531 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Father - Daughter, 1977; 209532 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Feminist Art Resource, undated; 209533 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Fernando's ID, ca 1985; 209534 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Film as Art (1/2), 1973-1976; 209535 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Film as Art (2/2), 1973-1976; 209536 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - FOTB, 1987-88 working notes, 1987-1988; 209537 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - FOTB (The Book Book), 1992; 209538 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - FOTB travel, 1987, 1989; 209539 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Gellerman, Hope, 1982-1986; 267659 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - General Conceptual, 1970,1972,1975; 209540 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - GS, undated; 209541 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (1/5), 1987-1989; 209542 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (2/5), 1989-1990; 209757 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (3/5), 1990-1991; 209758 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (4/5), 209759 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (5/5), 209760 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Gimblett, Max - Envelope, Undated; 209761 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Gloria - Sept. 13 - Oct. 20, 2002, 209762 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Going Virtual course description - NYU, Spring 2000, 209763 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Gomez, Edward - Fulbright Grant Reference Form, 1985; 209764 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Grantmakers and Avocus articles, 1993-1995 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Graphoanalysis (1/5), 1974-1977; 209765 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Graphoanalysis (2/5), 1974-1977; 209766 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Graphoanalysis (3/5), 1974-1977; 209767 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Graphoanalysis (4/5), Undated; 209768 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Graphoanalysis (5/5), Undated; 209769 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Green Folder (1/8); Nancy Reagan b/w [Marilyn Zimmara], undated; 209955 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Green Folder (2/8); Martha Wilson as Tipper Gore, 1993; 209956 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Green Folder (3/8); Tipper in PMI window 1994, 209957 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Green Folder (4/8) MW by Benita Abrams, undated; 209958 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Green Folder (5/8) Photos of MW, undated; 209959 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Green Folder (6/8) MW as Tipper Gore, 1993, 209960 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Green Folder (7/8) Ms. Magazine, 1996; 209961 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Green Folder (8/8) Orchids, 1974; 209962 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Greg Bregere, 1987-1994 (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Guerrilla Girls, 1993-1996 (Box 86, Folder 3-4)
    - Guggenheim app 2002, 209963 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Hamilton NAL Chapter XI, 1975, 1976; 209964 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Hemispheric Institute Anti-War Cabaret 7/17/03, 2003; 209965 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Heresies folder in Impractical folder, 1977; 209966 (Box 27, Folder 18)